# Wojciech Kasprzyk

# Senior Frontend Developer

I build web applications with a strong emphasis on optimization and user experience.

#### **About**

I am a big fan of application **performance optimization** and reactive programming. I love finding new, better ways to solve technical and business cases.

Over the past 7 years, I have worked on a diverse range of user-centric applications across multiple industries. My contributions include developing content management systems (CMS) tailored for the healthcare sector; creating web and mobile applications for fleet management that track thousands of vehicles for over 2000 organizations; designing a fluid management system for petrol retailers and buyers; building micro frontend applications for the real estate market, connecting buyers, brokers, and developers; and developing a suite of web and mobile solutions for managing city water networks, including early leak detection systems.

I love well-designed applications having UX that helps to solve user problems, and well-designed architecture having Developer Experience that helps to avoid future problems. So far I have Angular, NgRx, RxJs, Nx workspace, React, Storybook, Javascript, Typescript, HTML, CSS, SCSS, and Flutter under my belt. I used to work with Node.js, MongoDB, and Express.js (MEAN stack). I'm still enthusiastically grabbing onto other Frontend frameworks and libraries.

#### **Experience**

Senior Frontend Developer | VonRoll August 2023 - Now

> Developed a web application for visualizing and managing city water networks, including infrastructure and devices. Created related hybrid mobile apps, implementing specific features from the web application and extending them with additional functionalities.

SCSS **Angular** NgRx RxJs Nx Workspace **Angular Material** Map API Typescript Ionic

March 2022 - July 2023

Senior Frontend Developer | Codete (now Exadel Europe)

Developed micro frontend monorepo application for the real estate market, connecting buyers, brokers, and developers.

NgRx SCSS RxJs Nx Workspace Angular **Typescript Angular Material** Storybook

October 2019 - February 2022 Frontend Developer | Loycon Systems

Built the real estate market application connecting buyers, brokers, and developers.

- Built fleet management system allowing users to track devices mounted on objects working for heavy industry
- Built three cross-platform mobile applications to implement specific components of a fleet management system
- Focused on performance optimisation
- Handling thousands of data snapshots per device, for hundreds of devices per customer, across thousands of customers

SCSS **Angular Material** NgRx RxJs Map API PrimeNG **Angular Typescript Flutter** Dart

July 2017 - September 2019

Web Developer | Comarch Healthcare

Developed a CMS for the healthcare industry, featuring a patient portal for scheduling appointments and accessing medical documentation. Additionally, built a mobile application for health monitoring, similar to the iOS Health app, with seamless integration into the existing healthcare system.

Angular **Typescript** NgRx RxJs SCSS React Node.js Express.js MongoDB

### **Education**

October 2014 - July 2019

# AGH University of Science and Technology

- Master of Engineering Electronics and Telecommunications | Networks and Services
- Bachelor of Engineering Electronics and Telecommunications

# Tech stack

>5 years industry experience Things I'm great at **Typescript** SCSS NgRx RxJs **Angular** Things I'm good at >1 year industry experience Nx workspace Node.js Express.js MongoDB Storybook Flutter Dart Personal time, no industry Things I like a lot experience React React Native Figma

Just hyped about Things I would like to spend more on

> Cypress **Svelte** Solid.js Playwright Next.js